Any progress
Contacted his former security company
They also tried to access Qinghe Orphanage's old files
Stop them
Formally remind the relevant agencies
Personal files must not be leaked illegally
We can't let the Gu family dig into his past
Is this all you found after a whole day
Public records are scarce
His earlier records are basically blank
If he's just an ordinary bodyguard
How could he understand funding issues
We can't look into Qinghe Orphanage
Personal files are protected
Someone is protecting him
Chengze
Here is the first draft of the share authorization you wanted
Leave it there
Are you still investigating Fu Chenzhou
Something is off about him
Could he actually have some hidden identity
Hah if he were a big shot in Nancheng
I definitely would have heard of him
But what if he isn't from Nancheng
If he really isn't just an ordinary bodyguard
Did Su Mingyao know all along
This game might have been set up by him
from the moment the groom was replaced
and it's already out of our control
Aren't you tired after reading all afternoon
Tired but worth it